迈克:哦,那真是一场噩梦.
Mike: Oh, this is a nightmare.
当我向父母出售去欧洲旅行的票和我得了张免费票就开始了.
It all started when I sold my parents a trip to Europe and I got one
那就是我麻烦的开始.而且在那时侯我认识了艾米.
for free.That's when my troubles began.And that's when I met Amy.
艾米:你有没有意识到,按照我们的路线,
Amy: Do you realize that according to the itinerary,
我们将错过梵高墓了?
we're missing the grave of Van Gogh?
迈克:身体健康.
Mike: Guzenteit.
迈克:你能相信,
Mike: Can you believe she actually came all the way to Europe just to
她远道来欧洲只想看看坟墓和博物馆?
see a bunch of graves and museums?
艾米:你为什么来欧洲?
Amy: Why did you come to Europe?
迈克:我选择了一个地方,那儿6800万女人对我说的话一点不懂,
Mike: Well I figure a place with sixty eight million women who couldn't
也不是完全糟透了.
understand a word I said, couldn't be all bad.
迈克:当旅游公司破产后,她有些受不了.
Mike: And then when the tour went bust, she didn't take it too well.
艾米:我们是被陷在欧洲了.我们有两张回程票,
Amy: We are stranded in Europe.
只有在巴黎有效,
We have a pair of tickets that work only in Paris in six days,
有效期六天.一个离我们500英里的城市.
a city five hundred miles away.
迈克:于是我们开始步行.我是说,
Mike: So we started walking.I mean I thought we had some laughs along the way.
我认为一路上我还有欢乐.她看起来心情有点放松,
She seemed to be loosening up a little bit,
但我想我错了,因为放弃了我.艾米!
but I guess I was wrong because she deserted me.Amy!Amy!
艾米!因此我在这,
So here I am, broke and alone in Spain.
身无分文孤单一人在西班牙.我只是希望妈妈和爸爸的遭遇要比我好.
I just hope mum and dad are doing better than I am.
麦琪:这真是场噩梦,杰森和我一到了巴黎就,然后……啊!!
Maggie: This is a nightmare.No sooner did Jason and I get to Paris, then...urgh!!!
杰森:阑尾炎,但是我们带你去医院治疗.一切就会好的.
Jason: It's appendicitis but we are taking you to the hospital.Everything's going to be
fine
麦琪:对于这个繁华的城市,我看到的一切就是……
Maggie: And all I've seen of this gorgeous city is...
杰森:瞧.
Jason: Voila.
麦琪:而且最糟的是,
Maggie: And the worst part is,
我们不能在亨利宾馆举行我们的结婚纪念.我还是比较高兴,
we can't have our anniversary dinner at Henri's.
我父母在家帮忙照看孩子.
I'm just glad my folks are taking care of the kids back home.
开萝尔: 啊!(奶奶把我的脸用淤泥包裹,而迈克却在西班牙享受快乐.)
Carol: Ahhhh!(Grandma's frozen my face in beauty mud, while Mike's living it up in Spain.
迈克:艾米,不要跑了.艾米.
Mike: Amy stop moving.Amy.
杰森:这是长途电话,我得说得快点,行.我们正在医院,
Jason: This is long distance so I'll make it quick, alright.
阑尾炎.她的.感觉很好.返程航班不变.
We are in the hospital,appendicitis.Hers.Feeling fine.Return flight the same.
本:嘿,这太好了.
Ben: hey, this is great.You sound like you are calling from down the street.
你听起来就好像你是街上打来的.你再扔一个硬币试试看,
Can we try that thing where you drop the pin down by the receiver and
我能不能听得见?喂.
I see if I can hear it?Hello.
杰森: 14美元一分钟,但是他还胡闹.
Jason: Fourteen dollars a minute and he's playing games.
麦琪:杰森,克莉丝睡得好吗?
Maggie: Jason, is Chrissy sleeping alright?
杰森:是的,是的.为什么她会不好?她又不必睡在椅子上.
Jason: yes, yes.Why shouldn't she be?She doesn't have to sleep in that chair.
开萝尔:那么,什么事这么重要,他不能告诉我.
Carol: So, what was so important he couldn't tell me/
本:哦,没什么?只是妈妈阑尾炎进了医院.
Ben: Oh nothing, just that mum's in the hospital with appendicitis.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
克莉丝:本,本.都是你的错,外婆输的要晚上溜回家了.
Chrissy: Ben.Ben, it's your play and grandma's trying to shoot the moon.
本:那么我就不进去了.
Ben: Then I'm not going in there.
麦琪:在这一刻我不知道哪个更糟.是阑尾炎呢,
Maggie: so at this point I don't know what is worse.
还是杰森试图让我保持开心.
Having appendicitis or Jason trying to keep me entertained.
杰森:对我笑一下.再笑.别浪费每一分钟……
Jason: Shoe me that smile.Again.Don't waste another minute...
迈克:现在让我说,今天我走了27公里,
Mike: Now lets say, today I covered twenty seven kilometers,
也就是4英里还是40英里?
which is either four miles or forty miles.
没有人,照这种速度的话,
No man, I'm never going to make it to Paris in three days at this rate.
3天我是绝对走不到巴黎.
I just hope Amy is having as much trouble as I am.
我只希望Amy和我有一样多的麻烦.更希望她麻烦比我还多.
Heck I hope she's having more.
麦琪:你确定你需要在这?
Maggie: Are you sure you want to stay here?
杰森:亲爱的,我的腰疼有什么关系,
Jason: Honey, what does my lower back pain matter,
只要我能使你振作精神.
as long as I'm cheering you up.
麦琪:杰森,你为什么不开个房间?
Maggie: Jason, why don't you get a room?
杰森:什么?亲爱的,你在这里,
Jason: What?Honey, you're here and you're feeling miserable.
而且你感到痛苦.我也要在这,也感受痛苦.
I'm going to stay right here and feel miserable too.
麦琪:亲爱的,没有理由我们两个都错过巴黎风情.
Maggie: Honey, there's no reason that we should both Miss Paris.
杰森:谁错过巴黎了?
Jason: Who's missing Paris?We're not missing Paris.
我们并没错过巴黎.亲爱的,
Honey you had a croissant for dinner.
你吃的是新月形面包.
These nurses have all been very very rude to us.
这些护士对我们非常非常没有礼貌.
There's nothing more French than that.
没有什么比这更法国了.只要你把你的眼睛闭上,
If you just close you eyes,
就能听到穿过塞那河传来的音乐回声.
you can almost hear the sound of a concertina echoing across the Seine.
麦琪:我所听到的只是输液的声音.
Maggie: All I can hear is my drip bag.
杰森:那是你的问题,你们有想象力.
Jason: That's your problem, you can't visualize.
麦琪:杰森,照我说的,开个房间.
Maggie: Jason, like I said, get a room.
杰森:亲爱的,你知道我准备干什么吗?我准备明天早上去楼下的礼品店,买这个镇的每个景点的明信片.然后我们就假装去过那些地方.
Jason: Honey, you know what I'm going to do?I'm going to go down to
the gift shop tomorrow morning and I'm going to buy postcards of every
scenic place
in this town.And then we are going to pretend we are there
麦琪:有几分像去年的结婚纪念.
Maggie: Sort of like last years anniversary?
麦琪:谢谢,谢谢你告诉我为什么戴头盔法规是个好主意.
Maggie: Thank you, thank you for showing me why helmet laws are a good idea.
让我走,让我走,让我走!
Amy: Let me go, let me go!
迈克:艾米.
Mike: Amy.
艾米:让我走.
Amy: Let me go.
迈克:(坚持一分钟.我在说什么呢?我不能忍受她了.)
Mike: (hang on a minute.what I am saying?I can't stand her)
艾米:我不应该被这样对待.
Amy: I shouldn't be treated like this.
迈克:别担心,艾米.我来了.
Mike: Don't worry Amy.I am here.
艾米:你.远点.
Amy: You.Stay away.
迈克:警官,不管她干了什么?她都不是故意的.不是的.
Mike: Whatever she did officerio, she didn't mean it.Nada io.
艾米:我不认识这个加拿大人.
Amy: I do not know this Canadian.
迈克:先生,先生.这个女人是我丈夫.回家,回到孩子身边,亲爱的.
Mike: Scenore, senore.This woman is my espouso.Come home to the kids honey.
艾米:你刚才告诉他们我是你的丈夫.
Amy: You just told them I'm your husband
迈克:那本来就是.疯狂游戏.
Mike: That's it.Play crazy.
艾米:我不是……
Amy: I'm not...
警察:(西班牙语)你见过如此的吵架吗?他们一定结婚了.
Policemen: (in Spanish) Have you ever seen such a fight?They must be married.
迈克:哦喔.我刚使得你免蹲大狱.
Mike: Oh wo.I just kept you out of jail.
艾米:你这个蠢蛋.
Amy: You jerk.
迈克:别客气.
Mike: You're welcome.
艾米:我就想被拘捕.
Amy: I wanted to be arrested.
至少能洗个热水澡和晚上睡觉的床.
At least it would have been a hot shower and a bed for the night.
迈克:你疯什么疯?
Mike: What are you crazy?
你认为他们会带你去里兹宾馆过夜?有肮脏地板,
You think they're going to take you to the Ritz for the night?
一片干面包就算你幸运了.
You would have been lucky with a dirt floor and a piece of dry bread.
艾米:哦,是吗?
Amy: Oh yeah.And how does a guy who knows nothing about anything suddenly
对一切都一无所知道的人,怎么一下子变成了西班牙监狱方面的专家了.
become an expert on Spanish jails?
迈克:那是因为,我昨夜就是在一个监狱度过的.
Mike: Well, I slept in one last night.
艾米:你被拘捕的?
Amy: You got arrested?
迈克:是的.但是跟你不同,我可没想过被拘捕.
Mike: Yeah.But unlike you, I did not want to be arrested.
由于指控我偷鸡,他们拘捕了我.你认为那有趣吗?
They accused me of stealing a chicken.You think that's funny?
艾米:我认为十分有趣.
Amy: I think that's great.
迈克:那好.我不会给你什么鸡肉的.
Mike: well fine.I won't give you any of the chicken.
艾米:我不知道我们哪一个更值得同情.
Amy: I don't know which of us is more pathetic.
迈克:唉,至少我可以被拘捕.哪怕是当我不愿意的时候.
Mike: well at least I can get arrested.Even when I don't want to.
艾米:我再给你一次被拘捕的机会.
Amy: I'll give you that one.
迈克:你身上怎么这么湿?
Mike: Why are you so wet?
艾米:我在喷泉里.
Amy: I was in the fountain.
迈克:那你在那里面干什么呢?
Mike: What were you doing in there?
艾米:我希望被拘捕起来.
Amy: I wanted to get arrested.
而且至少我想我可以凉快一下和干净一点.我实在受不了没有合适卫生设施.
And at the very least I thought I could cool off and get clean.
我们一起旅行吧.
I don't cope too well without proper hygiene.Let's travel together.
迈克:嗨,听着,我们一定不会有更糟糕的事情了.
Mike: Hey look, we couldn't do any worse.
艾米:对此,我可不敢确定.
Amy: I'm not so sure about that.
迈克:我们没有时间相互审问了.
Mike: We don't have time to try.
艾米:好的,但是就到……
Amy: Ok, but just until...
迈克:就到巴黎为止.好.但是如果再有类似蠢蛋的强硬措辞的话,我就离开.好吧.不过你再用笨蛋之类的字眼,我立刻就走.
Mike: Until Paris.Ok.But anymore strong language like jerk, and I'm out of here.
艾米:我会尽量控制自己.
Amy: I'll try to control myself.
迈克:谢谢你.
Mike: Thank you.
艾米:我们走.迈克,你看什么呢?这钱是为穷人准备的.
Amy: let's go.Mike, what are you looking at?That money is for the needy.
迈克:啊哈.
Mike: Uh hu.
艾米:迈克!
Amy: Mike!
迈克:听着,要么我们拿到钱就有地方住,
Mike: Look, either we get some money for a place to stay,
要么被逮捕也有地方住.另外,你还可以解决卫生问题.
or are we get arrested and we get a place to stay.
我们不会失手.来吧.
Plus, you can take care of that hygiene problem.We can't lose.Come on.
艾米:啊!
Amy: Ah!
杰森:行了,按照明信片旅游,我们现在到哪了?你是否还想说些更疯狂的话,还是什么?
Jason: Alright, where were we in our Paris by post card tour?Or do you
want to play some more mad lips, or what
麦琪:杰森,我真心诚意的跟你说这些的.滚开.看看东西.做做事情.
Maggie: Jason, I say this with love and affection.Get out of here.See something.Do something.
杰森:不,不.没有你什么都不去.
Jason: No, no.Not without you.
麦琪:如果你不马上走,我就把我伤口的线给拆了.
Maggie: If you don't go soon, I'm going to rip my stitches out.
你在让我的恢复痛苦.
You're making my recovery miserable.
杰森:我只是想让你振作一点.瞧瞧这屋子,
Jason: I'm just trying to cheer you up.
就足够使得任何人意志消沉了.
Look at this room, it's enough to depress anybody.
麦琪:杰森,走吧.沿塞那河走走.
Maggie: Jason, go.Walk along the Seine.
看看蒙娜莉莎,你也许还能找到亨利饭店.我说真的呢.
See the Mona Lisa, you might even find Henri's.I mean it.
杰森:好.好的.
Jason: Ok.Alright.
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Good.
杰森:我去,我去.但是我不会得到享受的.
Jason: I'll go, I'll go.And I won't enjoy it.
迈克:那么你在想些什么呢?
Mike: So what are you thinking about?
艾米:内衣.
Amy: Underwear.
迈克:什么?
Mike: Pardon me?
艾米:我是说,衣服是比较干净了,
Amy: I mean our clothes are cleaner,
但是如果有一套新的…….就好了,算我没说.
but it would be nice to have a fresh pair of...never mind.
迈克:你是神经病,不是吗?
Mike: You're insane, aren't you?
艾米:什么?就是因为我注意卫生,
Amy: What?Because I care about cleanliness,
因为我担心去巴黎的事情?因为我不认为这些事情很好笑,
because I worry about getting to Paris?
拦车搭车,
Because I don't think it's funny thumbing for rides and crashing people's
或破坏别人的婚礼,或跳进傻乎乎的喷泉.
weddings, and jumping into stupid fountains.
迈克:行了.别开始吼叫和闹腾了.
Mike: Come on.Don't start yelling and hopping all up and down.
艾米:迈克漫无目的的来欧洲,
Amy: Mike.You came to Europe expecting nothing, and so you're missing nothing.
因此你就什么都没有错过.但是我在我的线路里有58个地方要去,
But I came with fifty eight places on my itinerary and I'm not going to
但是我一个也没有去看.
get to see one.
迈克:哦,跟你的情况一样,我也有在欧洲的计划.
Mike: Oh, well for your information I had lots planned here in Europe.
艾米:类如什么?想去看看每个有女人的海滩?
Amy: Like what?Hanging out on every topless beach?
迈克:绝对不是.而且你听过我抱怨过一次我所错过的吗?
Mike: Absolutely not.And have you heard me complain once that I missed that?
艾米:哦,是呀.去遍西班牙低档次的迪斯科.
Amy: Oh yeah.Checking out all the sleazy discos in Spain.
迈克:哦,行了,
Mike: Oh right, so what did you have planned that was so meaningful and
那么你计划了什么有意义和重要的事情?
important.
艾米:大教堂,哈斯建筑,我祖父母在考比结婚的小教堂,塞纳河,罗浮宫.
Amy: The Gaudi cathedral, Histilian architecture, the chapel where my grandparents were married in Corbay
The Rover Seine, The Louvre
迈克:哦,呀.说大话.
Mike: Oh yeah.Big talk.
艾米:大话!
Amy: Big talk!
迈克:嗨,听着,
Mike: Hey look, if I'm the one who's supposed to be so shallow and stupid,
如果我被认为那么浅薄和愚蠢,我怎么会坐在这,
how come I can sit here and just appreciate just being on this mountain?
欣赏山色?在美丽的天空和一个姑娘享受美妙的野餐.
Under a beautiful sky and having a great picnic with a girl.
而且我根本不在意自己的内衣.
And I'm not concerned about my underwear at all.
我告诉你,我当然也想有套新的.
Let me tell you I could certainly use a fresh pair.Alright fine.
行了.也许最好我们别再说这些.
Maybe it's better we just don't talk.
艾米:这是个美丽的地方,迈克.
Amy: This is a beautiful place Mike.
迈克:是呀.
Mike: Yeah.
艾米:瞧,迈克,启明星.许个愿吧.
Amy: Look Mike, the first star.Make a wish.
迈克:哦,许愿也在你的计划内?
Mike: Oh, are wishes on your itinerary?
艾米:你确定这些东西安全?
Amy: Are you sure these things are safe?
男人:比协和飞机还安全.
Man: Safer even than the Concorde.
迈克:那么你怎么确切知道能降落在巴黎?
Mike: Well how do you know for sure it's going to end up in Paris?
男人:我保证.
Man: Guarantee.
艾米:我们必须得坐这个?
Amy: Do we have to do this?
迈克:听着,由于时间和钱的缘故,我们必须这样做.
Mike: Look, for the kind of time and money we have, we've got to.
艾米:我只是不相信这个家伙的热气球.我是在说气球.
Amy: I just don't trust this guy's hot air.I was talking about the balloon.
迈克:哇!我真不敢相信.哇,
Mike: Wow!I can't believe this.Wow, this is amazing.Wow!
太令人惊奇了.哇!你需要我抱着你吗?
Do you want me to put my arms around you?
男人:不要,没关系.
Man: No, that's ok.
艾米:如果风一直刮,
Amy: If the wind keeps blowing,
这样我们也许可以看一眼考比的教堂.
then we might just catch a glimpse of that chapel in Corbay.
杰森:独自逛巴黎.是不错!
Jason: Enjoy Paris alone.Yeah right!
迈克:嗨,艾米,那就是了.那就是考比.哇喔喔.这个东西的刹车在哪呀?
Mike: Hey Amy that's it.That's Corbay.Wow wo, wo.Where's the break on this thing?
男人:……
Man: ...
迈克:地球,死亡,我们,哦!艾米,艾米,起来.
Mike: Earth, death, us oh!Amy Amy, wake up.
艾米:迈克,你在干什么呢?
Amy: Mike, what are you doing?We have less than an hour to get to Paris.
我们还只有一个小时的时间必须到达巴黎.如果我们错过那个航班,我们就得永远被陷在欧洲了.
If we miss that flight, we are going to be stranded in Europe forever.
艾米:嗨!
Amy: Hey!
迈克:这就是你祖父母结婚的地方?
Mike: This is where your grandparents got married?
艾米:43年前.
Amy: Forty three years ago.
迈克:好,这是你路线的第一个项目,
Mike: well this is the first item on you itinerary, so relax,
那么放松点,从容不迫地享受吧.
take your time and enjoy it.
好,
Ok, we got forty five minutes to hit the other forty seven.
我们还有45分钟时间去看其余47项.我认为我们可以做到.
I think we can do it.
医生:啊,你好,爸爸.
Doctor: Ah, bonjour papa.
麦琪:杰森,你去哪了?你说你7点钟回来的,
Maggie: Jason, where have you been?
现在是,恩,差五分7点.
You said you'd be back at seven and it's, um, five to.
杰森:唉,我以为你让我出去的.
Jason: Well I thought you wanted me to get out.
麦琪:的确我是这么说的.但我没想到你真会走.
Maggie: Well of course I said that.I didn't really think you'd go.
杰森:我还以为……
Jason: I just thought that...
麦琪:以为什么?以为你可以把我扔在这破屋里,
Maggie: Thought what?That you could leave me in this crummy room while
自己却出去享受巴黎美好时光,一个轻浮的城市?
you went out and had a wonderful time in Paris, the city of lights?
杰森:麦琪.
Jason: Maggie.
麦琪:你说你不会开心的.你答应的.
Maggie: You said you wouldn't have fun.You promised.
杰森:我找到亨利饭店了.
Jason: I found Henri's.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:是的.就在20年以前我们离开的的地方.
Jason: Yes.Exactly where we left it twenty two years ago.
我甚至点了印在酒瓶上的相同的菜单.
I even ordered off the same menus printed on the wine bottle.
麦琪:哦!真不错.
Maggie: Oh that figures.That just figures.
那真不错.你或许美餐一顿,
You probably had a wonderful dinner and a wonderful champagne,
还有醉人的香槟,而且和异国情调的妇女聊了聊.
and winning conversation with exotic women.
亨利:你还记得亨利饭店?啊,
Henri: You remember Henri?Ah Madame Seaver.
西维尔夫人.二十年过去了,你只是看起来更可爱了.
In twenty years you only look lovelier.
杰森:不,亨利,亨利.
Jason: No, Henri, Henri.
亨利:啊,西维尔夫人.
Henri: Ah.Madame Seaver.In twenty years you only look lovelier.
二十年过去了,你只是看起来更可爱了.现在可以上菜了吗?
May I serve you now?
麦琪:哦,杰森,
Maggie: Oh Jason, you are the sweetest,
你是一个女人所能拥有的最可爱,最最周到的丈夫.
most thoughtful husband a woman could ever have.
杰森:是呀,我这样说都已经好多年了.
Jason: Yeah, I've been saying that for years.
麦琪:杰森 西维尔,你愿意娶我吗?
Maggie: Jason Seaver, will you marry me.
杰森:我正在考虑之中.
Jason: I'm thinking about it.
迈克:哇,巴黎.我想我们最终出了西班牙.喔,
Mike: Wow, Paris.Well I think we've finally got out of Spain.Wo, wo.
喔.小心,莫里斯.我们可不想撞上这东西.
Easy Maurice.We don't want to hit this thing.
艾米:我在梦里见到这些.
Amy: I've dreamed of things like this.
迈克:嗨,塞纳河.还有巴黎圣母院,那是罗浮宫和凯旋门.我确信这些是你的路线上的47,48和49项.
Mike: Hey, the river Seine.And Notre Dame Cathedral and that is the Louvre and the Arc de triumph.Items forty seven, forty eight and forty nine on your itinerary I do believe.
艾米:啊,你能不能把我们降落到那漂亮的公园里.
Amy: Ah, can you please put us down in that beautiful park?
男人:行.
Man: Oui.
迈克:好,好,你能不能把我们降落到那漂亮的公园里?哦!哦!哦!小心放下,莫里斯.哦,哦,哦,哦,哦.
Mike: Ok fine, could you put wee down in that beautiful park?Wow, wow, wow
Set it down easy Maurice.Wo, wo, wo.Wo, wo
男人:当你们从篮子里出去,就这样.你们怎么说重量……啊!
Man: When you get out of the basket, that's it.How you say the weight..Ahhhh!
迈克:这是我第一个听得懂的法语.
Mike: Well that's the first French I've understood.
艾米:等等!我的包.我的睡袋!我从来没有想过我们能做到.
Amy: Wait!My bag.My nap sack.I never thought we'd do it.
迈克:我可一秒没怀疑过.嗨,
Mike: I never doubted it for a second.
听着,我们得赶紧坐地铁去戴高乐机场.
Hey listen, we've got to catch that metro to De Gaulle Airport.
艾米:不是戴高乐机场,是奥利机场
Amy: Not de Gaulle, Orly airport.
迈克:不,我不会搞错这个的.我核对过机票.明白吗?
Mike: No, I didn't screw this one up.I checked the ticket.See?
艾米:不,但是我的航班是从奥利机场起飞.明白吗?
Amy: No but my flight's leaving out of Orly.see?
迈克:哦!那么我想是该说再见的时候了.
Mike: Oh!Well then I guess this is goodbye.
艾米:我知道这次旅行对你而言并不愉快……
Amy: I know this trip wasn't a pleasure for you...
迈克:我不是故意破坏你整个假期的……
Mike: I didn't mean to ruin your whole vacation...
艾米:你先走.
Amy: You go first.
迈克:不,继续.
Mike: No go ahead.
艾米:你先走.这比我想象的还困难.
Amy: You first.This is harder than I expected.
突然之间我不会说再见了.
All of a sudden I can't say goodbye.
迈克:那么就别……就说行的.
Mike: Well then don't.Just say oui.
艾米:那是行的意思,迈克.
Amy: That means yes Mike.
迈克:我知道,可我懂的另一个法语单词是啊,
Mike: I know, but the only other word I know in French is ahhhhhh and
看起来在这不合适.
that doesn't seem appropriate.
艾米:给.这是我加州的地址.你认识字吧?
Amy: Here.This is my address in California.You can read can't you?
迈克:当然.
Mike: Yes.
艾米:谢谢你.不管你相信不相信,这是,这是…….
Amy: Thank you.Believe it or not, this was, this was...
迈克:快乐.
Mike: Fun.
艾米:是呀.我并不太难相处,是吗?
Amy: Yeah.I wasn't too much of a chore to be with, was I?
我是说,我可能很固执.我在努力改正.
I mean I can be so rigid.I am working on it.
迈克:继续努力.我想我们得出发了.
Mike: Keep working on it.I guess we got to go.
艾米:我会想念你的,迈克.
Amy: I'm going to miss you Mike.
我想还有一点值得说的是,
And for what it's worth, you're not the screw up you think you are.
你不是你想的那么振作.我说的是真心话.
And I mean that pretty much the way it sounds.
本:嗨,这是什么照片?
Ben: Hey, what's this picture?
迈克:那个发疯的西班牙人追我的小巷.
Mike: That's the alley where that crazy Spanish guy was chasing me.
本:这张呢?
Ben: This one?
迈克:在我跑的时候我所潜入的厕所.
Mike: That is the men's room where I ducked in on the run.
本:不错的小便池..
Ben: Nice urinal.
迈克:谢谢你.
Mike: Thank you.
本:这又是什么?
Ben: And what's this?
迈克:哦,这些是我的面部特写.他们通常不让你带这些东西.
Mike: Oh, they are my mug shots.They usually don't let you keep these things.
本:闪光不错.
Ben: Nice lighting.
迈克:谢了.
Mike: Thank you.
本:这宝贝是谁?
Ben: Who's the babe?
迈克:这是艾米 鲍德莉.我碰到的那个姑娘.
Mike: that is Amy Boudelay.That is the girl that I met.
是呀,一开始她让人觉得头疼,
Yeah, at first she was kind of a drag,
可后来她变得,有几分心疼.
and then later on she turned out to be, kind of a drag.
本:看来你的旅途并不开心.
Ben: It doesn't look like a very fun trip.
迈克:瞧,本,
Mike: look Bennie, you do not go to Europe just to have fun.
你去欧洲不仅仅是寻开心.你去那里是感受古老而丰富的文化.
You go there to experience an older richer culture.
本:还有小便池?
Ben: Any more urinals?
本:嘿!一定是爸爸妈妈.
Ben: Hey, that must be mum and dad.
迈克:啊,听着,
Mike: Ah, well listen Ben.
本.我真的认为我还没做好听他们讲述旅途.
I really don't think I'm ready to hear about their trip yet.Ok.
好.他们一定会责怪我卖给他们的可恶的旅行.好了,
They'll probably blame me for selling them the lousy tour.
如果他们问,就说我不在家.
Ok, if they ask, I'm not home.
本:继续.我能够对付妈妈爸爸.相信我.
Ben: Go on.I can handle mum and dad.Trust me.
迈克:好吧,谢谢.
Mike: Ok, thanks.
麦琪:嗨,本.你好吗?
Maggie: Hey Ben.How are you?
本:你们可回来了.
Ben: You guys are home.
杰森:是呀.
Jason: Yeah.
本:旅行怎么样?希望照片比迈克的更好.
Ben: Hhow was your trip?Hope the pictures are better than Mike's.
杰森:迈克在家?
Jason: Mike's home?
本:恩,
Ben: Um, Mike who.
迈克?为什么要浪费时间谈论一个不在这儿的人呢?
Why are we wasting our time talking bout someone who's not even here?
还是看看那些照片吧.
Let's see those darn pictures.
麦琪:对不起,本.没有照片.不过我有很多明信片.
Maggie: Well sorry Ben.No pictures.But I do have plenty of postcards.
本:嗨,你们看了那么多幽雅的地方?
Ben: Man, you guys saw a lot of neat stuff.
麦琪:一个也没.
Maggie: Not any of it.
克莉丝:妈咪,爸爸.
Chrissy: Mummy, daddy.
杰森:我的小宝贝.
Jason: My baby.
麦琪:克莉丝.
Maggie: Chrissy.
外婆:感谢上帝,你们回来了.我打破的东西列了个清单.
Grandma: Thank god you are back.I wrote a check for the thingy I broke.
大多数孩子都在家,我想.这星期我一直庆幸的是埃迪两天前就走了.
Most of your children are here I think.
哦,别担心.
The only good thing about this week is Ed left two days ago.
我乘出租车.再见.再见.
Oh,don't worry, I'll take a cab.See you.Bye!
克莉丝:我认为这星期外婆过的不好.
Chrissy: I think grandma's had a tough week.
本:喂!
Ben: Hello.
开萝尔:比我想的更糟,本.爸爸和妈妈彻底失踪了.
Carol: It's worse than I thought Ben.Mum and dad have completely disappeared.
这样的话,看来我不得不在这儿待上几星期了.本:爸爸,
At this rate it looks like I may have to stay here a couple of weeks.
我认为你最好来处理这事.00:22:23,900
Ben: Dad, I think you better handle this one.